let qa = [
    {
        id: 1,
        question: "What is JS?",
        ans: "A.JS means JavaScript.Javascript is a both scripting and programing language and it is loosely typed in nature ,it can be used in both front end and back end .It is used to make websites interactive with the users."
    },
    {
        id: 2,
        question: "What is CSS?",
        ans: "A.CSS means Cascading Style Sheet."
    },
    {
        id: 3,
        question: "What is the difference b/w var , let and const keywords?",
        ans: "A.in var declaration , initialization , re initialization and redeclaration is possible.in let redeclaration is not possible .in const re initialization and redeclaration is not possible ."
    },
    {
        id: 4,
        question: "What are the different datatypes we use in javascript?",
        ans: "A.1.Primitives(predefined) and non-Primitives(user defined).Primitives(predefined)	: number , string , boolean , null and undefined non-Primitives(user defined): Arrays , Objects , Strings , functions ."
    },
    {
        id: 5,
        question: "What is the difference b/w null and undefined?",
        ans: "A.undefined is the value of a variable which is declared in javascript and not being initialized with any value. Datatype of undefined variable is also undefined.null is a keyword which makes a variable memory as empty.Datatype of null variable is object ."
    },
    {
        id: 6,
        question: "What is typeof operator in javascript?",
        ans: "A.typeof operator is used to check the datatype of a variable ."
    },
    {
        id: 7,
        question: "What is the difference b/w == and ===?",
        ans: "A. == is a relational operator it checks only the values(it is not a stricktly checking optr).=== is also a rel optr , it checks both values and the datatypes(it is stricktly checking optr) ."
    },
    {
        id: 8,
        question: "What are functions in javascript and types of functions ?",
        ans: "A.1.General/Named/Normal function 2.Anonymous function 3.Arrow functions 4.CallBack function 4.Immediate Invoking function ."
    },
    {
        id: 9,
        question: "What is Array?",
        ans: "A.Javascript Array is a set of Homogenous or Heterogenous elements , it used to store multiple values into a single varaible ."
    },
    {
        id: 10,
        question: "what is innerHTML and innerText?",
        ans: "A.innerText and innerHTML are the DOM properties.innerText will return only the text from a html tag but innerHTML returns text along with the sub tag used inside a tag ."
    },
    {
        id: 11,
        question: "What is html?",
        ans: "A.Html is a markup language it ius used to create the structure of web pages ."
    },
    {
        id: 12,
        question: "what is the difference b/w forof and forin loop?",
        ans: "A.forof : it will be undefined. forin: it will remove empty spaces ."
    },
    {
        id: 13,
        question: "What is DOM?",
        ans: "A.DOM stands for document object model ."
    },
    {
        id: 14,
        question: "Methods of Dom?",
        ans: "A.The Methods to acces html elements in DOM:document.getElementById(),document.getElementsByTagName(),document.getElementsByClassName(),document.querySelector(),document.querySelectorAll() ."
    },
    {
        id: 14,
        question: "What is callback functon?",
        ans: "A.callback function is nothing but passing a function as an argument to another function ."
    },
    {
        id: 16,
        question: "What is an object?",
        ans: "A.An Object is a realtime entity , which will have its own states and behaviours. and there will be gradually changes in thier states and behaviours ."
    },
    {
        id: 17,
        question: "What is destructuring in javascript?",
        ans: "A.Destructuring is the process of unpacking values from arrays or objects and storing into distinct variables in order to access the values in meaningfull way ."
    },
    {
        id: 18,
        question: "What is box model?",
        ans: "A.box model is a layout of the html elements on the web page it consits of content , padding , border and margin ."
    },
    {
        id: 19,
        question: "What are display and position properties",
        ans: "A.display : inline , block , inlone-block , flex , grid ::position : static , sticky , fixed , absolute , relative ."
    },
    {
        id: 20,
        question: "What is the the difference b/w div tag and span tag?",
        ans: "A.div is a block level and it will have default margins , span is a inline element which is not having any default margin ."
    }
]
export default qa